oldnational.com 2010-11-12

# Privacy Policy - Old National

## Old National Bank Privacy Policy

#### What does this Privacy Policy cover?

Our concern for safekeeping your personal information goes far beyond this brochure. Our Privacy Policy covers the practices of all affiliates within the Old National family* - including our banking, insurance, investment and financial planning, asset management and trust service companies. It applies to all personally identifiable information about you that is obtained by Old National (“personal information”). At any time you decide to close your account or become an inactive customer, we will continue to adhere to the procedures described in this notice and any proper opt-out requests you make. This Privacy Policy also serves as our Privacy notice. This Privacy Policy contains important information about your choices in relation to certain information sharing and marketing offers within the Old National family of companies. You should be sure to review carefully the “Sharing Information Within Old National” section and your ability to opt out as set forth in this policy. **This policy does not apply to business or commercial customers.**

#### Recognition of a customer’s expectation of privacy

You regard your personal information as yours, and so do we. Because we do not sell or share your information with third parties not associated with services or activities of Old National (except as allowed by law), there is no need for you to tell us not to share your personal information with non-affiliated third parties. 

#### Collection, retention and use of customer information

We collect and use various types of information to service your accounts, save you time and money and better understand your needs. We collect personal information about you from the following sources:

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others
  * Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency

#### Security standards

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the integrity and confidentiality of your information. Old National also limits access to your nonpublic personal information to those employees who need to know that information in order to provide products and services to you. All our employees are trained to understand and comply with these information principles.

#### Maintenance of accurate information

Old National has implemented internal controls and procedures designed to maintain accurate records concerning your personal information. Should you ever believe that our records contain inaccurate, incomplete or non-current information about you, please notify us. We will respond to requests to correct the information in a timely manner.

#### Disclosure of information to nonaffiliated third parties

We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to nonaffiliated third parties, except as permitted by law as described below.

#### Service providers and joint marketing agreements

We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described under the heading “Collection, Retention and Use of Customer Information,” to companies that perform marketing or other services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements.

#### Beneficiaries of trusts

Certain information, such as fiduciary information, is subject to more restrictive information sharing limitations than other types of information, both internally and externally. If you have questions regarding fiduciary information, please contact your Trust Relationship Manager.

#### Looking out for children

We recognize that protecting children’s identities and privacy is important. We comply with the practices established under the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. We do not knowingly market to or solicit information from children under 13 without parental consent.

#### Sharing as required by law

We may disclose information to nonaffiliated third parties as allowed by law. For example, this may include a disclosure in connection with a subpoena or similar legal process, a fraud investigation, recording of deeds or trust and mortgages in public records, an audit or examination, or the sale of your account to another financial institution. We may also share information: 

  * If you initiate a request for us to share information with an outside party
  * If the information is provided to help complete a customer-initiated transaction

#### Sharing information within Old National

The Old National family of companies consists of financial service providers and the number of companies may change from time to time. There are no nonfinancial companies, or other organizations within the Old National family of companies, with whom we share information. We share the personal information that we collect about you within the Old National family in order to:

  * Provide customer service or account maintenance; or
  * Tell you about other products or services offered by Old National that we believe you will find useful. 

We may share information about our experiences or transactions with you or your account, such as account balance, payment history and services purchased, among our Old National family of companies. Additionally, unless you tell us not to as described below, we may also share other information about you not based on our transactions or experiences with you within our family of affiliates. This “non-experience information” includes information that is used, expected to be used, or collected for the purpose of establishing your eligibility for consumer credit, insurance and deposit accounts, including information:

  * From your applications, such as your income, assets or marital status; 
  * From a credit report, such as your credit score or credit history; 
  * From sources used to verify representations made by you, such as open lines of credit or employment history. 

#### Notice of your opportunity to opt out of certain information sharing and marketing within the Old National family of companies

If you prefer that we not share non-experience information about you within the Old National family of companies, you may opt out; that is, you may direct us not to share this information by calling us toll-free at 1.800.731.BANK (2265), option 0, then option 2.

Note: Your opt out decision in the above paragraph covers certain information about you that we might otherwise share with our corporate family. However, we may share other types of information about you as permitted by law.

You may also limit members of the Old National family of companies from marketing their products or services to you based on information that is shared with them by other Old National companies, such as your income, your account history with us and your credit score, by calling us toll-free at 1.800.731.BANK (2265), option 0, then option 2.

Note: Your opt out decision in the above paragraph does not apply in certain circumstances, such as if you currently do business with one of our affiliates or if you ask to receive information or offers from them.

Your decision to opt out will continue until it is revoked by you. If you have already notified us of your election to opt out, you do not need to contact us unless you choose to modify your previous directive.  For any accounts that you hold jointly with another person, each person may separately opt out and joint account holders may opt out for each other. If only one joint account holder opts out, we may share information about the other joint account holders.

#### Other privacy protections

You may have other privacy protections under some state laws. We will comply with applicable state laws as to information about you. For example, certain state laws may restrict the types of information we may disclose about you or require us to provide you with an additional notice.

We will not use or share personally identifiable medical information for any purpose other than the underwriting or administration of your insurance account, policy or claim, unless otherwise required or permitted by law.

#### USA Patriot Act

To help the government fight the funding of terrorism and money laundering activities, the USA Patriot Act requires all financial institutions to obtain, verify and record information that identifies each person (including business entities) who opens an account. What this means for you: When you open an account, we will ask for your name, physical address, date of birth, tax payer identification number and other information that will allow us to identify you.

We may also ask to see your driver’s license or other identifying documents. We will let you know if additional information is required.

#### Keeping up-to-date with our privacy policy

We will provide notice of our privacy policy annually, as long as you maintain an ongoing relationship with us. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time upon proper notice to you. You may view our policy and a current listing of our family of companies on our web site at oldnational.com or contact us for another copy. 

#### Protecting what's yours

When you share your personal information with a financial partner, you expect that information to remain safe and secure. And well you should. After all, you own this information as surely as you own a home or the money in your bank account. Rest assured, Old National understands this very well.

As your full-service financial partner, we want to inform you about our comprehensive Privacy Policy and how it protects you, every day. This brochure details the daily practices that allow us to safeguard one of your most valuable assets: trust.

*Old National family of companies   
The following is a list, as of December 31, 2009, of the Old National subsidiaries and affiliates to which this policy applies:

Old National Bank   
Old National Insurance   
Old National Investments   
Old National Trust Company   
Old National Wealth Management   
ONB Benefits Administration, LLC   
ONB Finance Company, Inc.   
ONB Insurance Agency, Inc.   
ONB Insurance Group, Inc.   
American National Trust and Investment Management Co.   
Employee Plans, LLC   
JWF Specialty Co.   
Regional Title Services, LLC

oldnational.com   
1.800.731.BANK   
NYSE: ONB

Rev. 12/09  
Copyright &#169; 2009 Old National Bancorp; All Rights Reserved.
